{
  "tasks": [
    {
      "id": "01234",
      "datetime": "12.10.2022",
      "progress": 40,
      "measurements": [
        {
          "id": "0",
          "done": true
        },
        {
          "id": "1",
          "done": false
        }
      ],
      "medications": [
        {
          "id": "0",
          "time": "20:33",
          "done": false
        },
        {
          "id": "1",
          "time": "22:33",
          "done": true
        }
      ],
      "lifelogs": [
        {
          "id": "0",
          "question": "question_000",
          "answers": ["yes", "no", "neither"],
          "isShowed": true,
          "topic": "lifelog_000"
        },
        {
          "id": "1",
          "question": "question_001",
          "answers": [],
          "isShowed": true,
          "topic": "lifelog_001"
        },
        {
          "id": "2",
          "question": "question_002",
          "answers": ["neither"],
          "isShowed": true,
          "topic": "lifelog_002"
        },
        {
          "id": "3",
          "question": "question_003",
          "answers": [],
          "isShowed": true,
          "topic": "lifelog_003"
        },
        {
          "id": "4",
          "question": "question_004",
          "answers": ["no", "no"],
          "isShowed": true,
          "topic": "lifelog_004"
        },
        {
          "id": "5",
          "question": "question_005",
          "answers": [],
          "isShowed": true,
          "topic": "lifelog_005"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "01234",
      "datetime": "13.10.2022",
      "progress": 50,
      "measurements": [
        {
          "id": "0",
          "done": true
        },
        {
          "id": "1",
          "done": true
        }
      ],
      "medications": [
        {
          "id": "0",
          "time": "20:33",
          "done": false
        },
        {
          "id": "1",
          "time": "22:33",
          "done": true
        }
      ],
      "lifelogs": [
        {
          "id": "0",
          "question": "question_000",
          "answers": ["yes", "no", "neither"],
          "isShowed": true,
          "topic": "lifelog_000"
        },
        {
          "id": "1",
          "question": "question_001",
          "answers": [],
          "isShowed": true,
          "topic": "lifelog_001"
        },
        {
          "id": "2",
          "question": "question_002",
          "answers": ["neither"],
          "isShowed": true,
          "topic": "lifelog_002"
        },
        {
          "id": "3",
          "question": "question_003",
          "answers": [],
          "isShowed": true,
          "topic": "lifelog_003"
        },
        {
          "id": "4",
          "question": "question_004",
          "answers": ["no", "no"],
          "isShowed": true,
          "topic": "lifelog_004"
        },
        {
          "id": "5",
          "question": "question_005",
          "answers": [],
          "isShowed": true,
          "topic": "lifelog_005"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}  